Are you guys a
couple?
Yes. We
are.
Yeah. Would you mind sharing a picture of how you guys first
met? We met on Bumble in
Dallas. We live in Dallas There you
go.
Weekend. And we met our well, his family has a dog, and, that's how we have
Bowen. What's his what's her
name?
Beau.
Beau. How old is
she?
Two.
Two. It's
okay. So what was your first impression of
her? First impression of
her? I mean, she's
gorgeous. I'm just
looking.
Right.
Yeah. What what would you
say? He was very charming and very
sweet.
Okay. And how long you guys been in a relationship
for? Five
years. Five years
in? Five years
in. My favorite thing about
him? His heart, and he's very
kind.
I
see. What did you
say? Her sense of
humor. Sense of
humor? Sense of
humor.
Oh.
Nice. If somebody's getting into a relationship today, what advice would you guys give to
them?
What
advice? Be open and
honest. There you
go. There you have
it. Be open and
honest. I
see.
Okay. That
helps. Your
intentions.
What? Come
again? Open and
honest. Got your
intentions.
Right. That's
nice.
Okay. And if if you guys are open sharing your name, and what do you do
following? Lauren, I've been type of
sales. I'm
Jordan. I'm a customer success manager for a construction tech
company. Oh,
perfect.
Alright. Thank you,
guys. Have a great
day. Thank
you.